Kristen, we we saw your uh uh what your
family's reaction would be if you got
drafted by the Falcons. How they
handling that?
>> Say it again, sir.
>> How how how is the family handling uh uh
uh the rival Saints? Are they going to
they going to they going to be converts?
>> Yeah, they they got to convert. You
know, they they they Dirty Birds fans.
We We ain't the Dy Birds no more. We f
we Saints now. We Saints now. It's up.
It's up. I told him. My uncle just told
me. He said, "Man, I guess I got to be a
Saints fan." I said, "Yeah, you got to
be. You don't got no choice. Let's go.
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, how much had you uh
talked to this team, thought about this
team, and and and how do you like,
>> man? To be real with y'all, I talked to
the um Saints at the uh combine. We had
a great interview. They challenged me a
lot. Very challenging. Stood on 10. I
love that they challenged me. Um it was
it kind of felt like Georgia being in
that room. They run the same defense
like Georgia. So, it's it's a no-brainer
at day one. Easy learn, easy clean up.
And um yeah, we we barely talked the
whole time. like we barely talked.
That's why I was just like it was a
happy surprise. I'm like, "Dang, I'm
going to the Saints. Let's go."
>> Before the during the draft process, you
said that uh running through somebody's
face was your favorite part of the pass
rush. What else do you like uh when it
comes to your style of play on the
interior?
>> Man, I just like being a Swiss Army
knife. I feel like anything my coach
tell me to do, I can do it. From from
being dominant, from being dominant in
the uh in the inside at nose, from being
dominant at the three tech position,
dominant the four eye, dominate the
five. I can just do everything. And I
think I just bring that versatility to
the game. And just my mindset, uh I
think my mindset is just second to none.
I think I got the best mindset in the
class in terms of just like I want to
run through somebody's face. I seek
physicality. I want physicality. And
that's just what I was taught. That's
how I always been. And that's what I'm
on. That's what I live by.
Christian, you've been down here for the
Sugar Bowl. Uh, what's your thoughts on
the city and the fan base down here?
>> Man, I love the city. I love them glazed
beignets. I gotta stay away from them,
though. I got I gota I gotta stay away
from them. I'mma kind of just portion
that out a little bit. But I love the
city of New Orleans, man. It's a city of
camaraderie. I think the whole city come
together. I was just telling one of my
homeboys a couple weeks ago, I said,
"Man, next year I cannot miss Marty
Gro." And guess what? I'mma be down
there. So, it's perfect. I I'm going to
be right there in the building. But, uh,
it's just the culture down there. It's
It's special. Um it's not like nobody
else. Um what they building is special
down there with the Saints and um I get
to play against I get to play against
some dogs in that in that conference.
And I get to play with Brian Braz. So
I'm excited. I'm excited.
>> What stands out to you about Brian?
>> Man, he a dog. He a dog. I've been
watching Brian since high school. Like
when I say since high school throwing
kids around in them highlight videos
that was going viral every week just
like he a dog. His mindset like his
mindset he's just relentless. And I
think us two together it's going to be a
movie. I'll tell you. I ain't gonna do
too much talk about that, but it's gonna
be a movie. So,
>> Kristen, what's uh what's your day been
like here leading up to this? And uh
where you at? Who you celebrating with?
>> Say it again, sir.
>> What What's your day been like leading
up to this?
>> Man, my day been a blessing. I woke up
this morning, had a good breakfast. I
went to go work out, went to tomorrow,
had to get some more more little tweak
ups for my fit. Um and came back. Now
I'm with the family. We having a good
time. We turned up. I can't complain.
>> You said the Saints uh challenged you.
How did they challenge you?
>> They just wanted to see where my mind
was at. I think the Saints is a very
they they they're big on mentality. And
I think that's why I'm here. No, not no
thanks. I know that's why I'm here.
Mentality. I think they wanted to see
where my mentality was at. They wanted
to see can I can I withstand hard
conversations? Can I withstand um hard
topics? Can I take hard coaching in that
meeting room? And I think I stood on
business. And I think that's just who I
am as a person. I want to be coached
hard. Um, I I want to learn. I seek
learning. And I think that's just what I
bring to the table. And I think that's
where they value that. They value me at.
>> Was some of that Bo Davis? Did you meet
with him?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Coach Bo, he he challenged
me for so, but Coach Bo just want to
win. And I think um he know Coach Scott,
my old Dline coach from Georgia. He they
very they're very close. They know each
other very well and they run the same
thing. So, he just kind of wanted to see
where my mind was at, where my heart was
at. And uh yeah, it was a good moment
for sure.
>> I I don't know the timet if he was in
college at the time you were coming out.
I mean, like did did you know him? Did
he recruit you?
>> He didn't. He didn't recruit me and
I'mma tell him about that, too. He
didn't recruit me, but Yeah, I'm I'm
I'mma tell him about that when I see
him. He didn't recruit me, but uh we
definitely knew of each other for sure.
Yes, sir.
>> Christie, playing for Kirby Smart in the
SEC, how did that prepare you for this,
>> man? Just playing for Coach Smart
prepared me each and every day, man.
Coach Smart when I he he only went 5'9,
510 on a good day. Um and just a
fireball. crazy, passionate, and he
wants his guys to show up every day and
be ready to learn, be ready to bring
that intensity and um just be ready to
win. I think not only winning on the
football field, but winning in life. And
I think that's what he brought into the
culture of Georgia, that's what he
brought into us. And I feel like having
him in the coach, it kind of challenged
me, especially as a freshman, he
challenged me so hard every day. And I
think that's why I am who I am right
now. So, I mean, it's nothing but a
blessing for sure. Nothing but a
blessing. Chris, obviously the the your
bio, your snapshot always says, you
know, run tackle, run stopper first. Um,
you know, how how true is that that that
that's an elite trait for you, but uh
how much better do you think you can get
at the other aspects of the game?
>> Man, I think I can get even even more
better at run stopping. I think I I got
to make all the plays that come to me. I
got to go through the process more. I
got to um go through my first gap, go
through my second gap, and go make the
plays. And I think I got I ain't even
reached my potential yet. I'm just
scratching the surface. got so much more
in the tank. I got to get better at run
stopping. I got to get better at pass
rushing. I got to get better at a lot of
that things. But one thing I do bring to
the table is is just that mindset and
that uh camaraderie, being a good
teammate, having a good mindset, and
just just wanting all the smoke. That's
just me.
>> Kristen, did you consider coming out
last year in the
>> Yes, sir. I did. I did.
>> What do you make of that decision now to
go back and do what you did at Georgia
then and end up where you ended up?
>> It's it's honestly the best decision I
ever made because I could have left. I I
could have I could have went to the NFL
last year, but um that that was the easy
way out for me. I wanted to be
challenged. I wanted to come back and
see how can I be a better pro in college
because I I already mastered Georgia. I
wanted to master the NFL. So, I think
that was my mindset was at the whole
time, just trying to see, okay, how can
I better myself, being a good noteaker
in the meeting room, being attentive in
the walkthroughs, being a good teammate,
just all those things. And I want to get
my degree, which I got, which I'm so
proud of. I was a team captain. Um, we
lost in the Sugar Bowl two times in a
row. So, trust me, I got a bad taste in
my mouth in that stadium and we gonna
turn that around for sure. We gonna turn
that around for sure. So, uh, just just
um just wanted to come back and just
challenge myself the whole 360. I think
as a man
if you're not trying to challenge
yourself, you're not a man. If you're
not if you're not willing to look
yourself in the mirror and ask yourself,
how can I get better? What do I do
wrong? And be your own critic, I feel
like
you already reach your peak. And for me,
I want to keep on scratching the
surface. So that's why that's why I
think about that.
>> What were some of the hallmarks for you
about when you said uh you wanted to
become a pro in college? What were some
of the things you wanted to achieve to
to get there?
>> I think the the biggest thing is showing
up every day. I think the power of
showing up is so important because
people don't understand showing up in
all aspects of life is important. Like
if when you show up, it changes so much.
And then when you show up and you're
attentive and you want to be there, it's
pre is it's is it's is known. It's is
one of the powerful things in the world.
So I think for me it's just showing up
every day having the same mentality.
Even when it was hard, even when some
days I was tired. Even when Sundays I
felt like I couldn't go no more. That's
when I had to power through. That's when
I had to really question who I was and
really, you know, stand on business. So
for me, it's really those it's it's them
hard days is showing up. I think that's
the first thing, just showing up and
just being a pro. And I think second
thing is uh
just being a leader. I think when people
hear a leader, they think, "Oh, man.
Coach coming. Let me be a leader." No,
being a leader is is is having fun. It's
being yourself. It's being able to tell
your teammates what they got to work on.
It's allowing somebody to hold you
accountable cuz leaders got their days,
too. And I think that's just what my
mindset and just going into that season.
I just want to do simple better. I want
to just grow. I want to win. And um
Yeah. Yeah.
>> Your high school team is the Saints.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir. It's crazy. Ain't
that crazy? Ain't that crazy right
there? Hey, God working in mysterious
ways. Look, I give it all to him. That's
crazy. See the Gro Saints, New Orleans
Saints. That's crazy. That's crazy.
>> What was your uh what did you get your
finish your degree in?
>> Housing managements.
So, if y'all want a house in the future,
y'all call me. Y'all just let me know.
>> What led you down that route?
>> Yeah, y'all just let me know. We'll
talk.
What uh what led you down that route,
>> man? Honestly, I came in wanting to be a
theater student, but uh I think it was a
conflict of interest with my schedule.
So, I said, "You know what? I like to
talk. I'm social, very art, I can
articulate my words. I'm very smart."
So, I said, "You know what? Let me just
do the same thing, but just do it in the
housing world." So, I just took it went
to the housing world. Um Dr. Scobad
Georgia, she did a hell of a job just
just um allowing me just to come in and
do extra time and put extra work in cuz
when you got a football schedule, you're
not really as attentive as you need to
be in the classroom. So, she allowed me
to come in after practice and do private
studies and work with her and her
teaching me the housing game and
teaching me all the little things. It it
was a blessing just having her in my
life, Miss Shirley Brown, too. Um and
that was my community and and they they
understood at first I didn't want to do
it because I really wanted to be a
theater student, but they understand
like Chris, things happen. We need to
understand that you came here for a
reason. It's to get your degree and go
to the league. We got we got to do the
first one. So, shout out to them for
real. I I love them and I appreciate
them.
>> Hey, Chris, when you go back to your uh
your high schools, the injury you had
early on, they said you might not play
again. How much does that make you
appreciate just where you are right now?
>> Man, you you never know. You never know
what you got till you lose it. Like, you
never know what you got till you lose
it. And um for me it was just like being
in that moment I really question myself
like as a football player I feel like
sometimes we make football our
everything our personalities we we make
it our our identity and and and and I
had to tell myself in that moment like
who am I? I questioned myself cuz they
told me I could never play again. I was
like dang this all I ever knew. So for
me it was it kind of came to a point
where I was like Chris you got to
understand something. Football is what
you do. It's not who you is. You
Christian middle at the end of the day.
And I think after that, it made me not
take the game for granted. It made me
not take the locker room for granted,
not take the coaching for granted, not
take the neighborhood for granted, the
the the the long hard workouts, the long
hard days for granted. And for me, it
it's it's a blessing. And after that,
when they told me I could play again,
it it was over from there. I took it up
a notch. And yeah, shout out Coach Pat
for that.
>> Take a couple more, guys.
What's your name?
>> All good.
>> Congrats, Christian. Congrats.
>> Okay, cool,
>> man. Thank y'all. I'll see y'all soon,
man. I'll see y'all soon.
>> Let's go. Uh, mad.